adspeed.net 2019-04-16

# Ad Servers | Ad Server Software | Ad Serving Software – Privacy Statement for AdSpeed.com

AdSpeed.com (AdSpeed) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy. The following document discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We have a separate Privacy Statement for advertisements served by AdSpeed on other websites. 

#### Information Collection and Use

If you do not sign up for an AdSpeed account, we do not collect your personal information. 

If you sign up for an AdSpeed account, we collect your personal information such as name, email, company name, and website URL. Additionally, if you purchase a paid subscription, we will collect your credit card, billing address, and telephone number to process payments.

We do not sell, share or disclose your personal information with any third-party entity excepted when required by law. AdSpeed may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Your email address is used only for communication between you and AdSpeed, including but not limited to technical support, customer service, billing inquiry, lost password recovery, newsletters, and account notices.

#### Information Automatically Logged

When you use our website, our server automatically records certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. The server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, referring page URL, platform type, the date and time of your request. 

We use this information to secure, administer, and improve our website and protect against unauthorized access. This information is not shared with any third-party entity excepted when required by law. We also use Google Analytics to anonymously track website usage and activity.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active in order to provide you with our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. If you wish to delete your account or request that we no longer use your information, please contact us. 

#### Browser Cookies

AdSpeed uses browser cookies, text data files stored within your browser, to allow or decline access to the appropriate person(s). The browser cookie helps our server know that you are an authorized user and let you navigate around the protected area of our website. For visitors, we use browser cookies to improve our website navigation. We do not track visitors through different websites once you leave AdSpeed. We also use Google Analytics to anonymously track website usage and activity. Google Analytics has its own cookie files. 

#### Newsletter Opt In/Out

You have an option to subscribe (opt-in) to our email newsletter. You may unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time by clicking the link at the bottom of each newsletter message. 

#### External and Third-Party Links

This website contains external links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of such websites to understand how they collect and use your data. This Privacy Statement only applies to information collected by our website(s). 

#### Spyware and Deceptive Advertising

Our Terms of Service describe our policies against spyware, adware and deceptive advertising. We take actions promptly to protect your privacy and our own reputation. Learn more

#### Children

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child, we will deactivate and delete that account. 

#### General

By registering as a member of our service, you are agreeing to accept this privacy policy. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time prior to any notice. It is your own benefit to check for any update of the policy in case we have not yet notified our members. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the practices of AdSpeed, please contact us.
